Guide To the University Of California, Santa Cruz Contemporary Classical Collection ARS.0103
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Unusual Items, 92 audiotape reel(s)
  - Barber; Moran; Gilbert; Winkler, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 8)
    Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Concertos, piano, orchestra, op. 38. Browning, piano; Boston Symphony Orchestra, Leinsdorf, conductor. Fall 1962.
    Moran, Robert. Bombardments.
    Amy, Gilbert; Filharmonia Narodowa (Warsaw, Poland); Markowski, Andrzej, 1924-1986; Winkler, Peter, 1943-; Stroud, Robert; Libet, Julian; Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981; Browning, John, 1933-2003; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993; Moran, Robert
  - Becerra; Diez; Irino; Orrego-Salas; Porter, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 12)
    Becerra-Schmidt, Gustavo, 1925-2010. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 5. Claremont String Quartet.
    Porter, Quincy, 1897-1966. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 6. Claremont String Quartet.
    Maturana, Eduardo, 1920-2003. Micropiezas. Claremont String Quartet.
    Orrego-Salas, Juan, 1919- Sextet, piano, clarinet, violins (2), viola, cello, op. 38. Miranda, piano; Drucker, clarinet; Claremont String Quartet.
    Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980. Sinfonia.
    Claremont String Quartet; Miranda, Mario; Drucker, Stanley; Becerra-Schmidt, Gustavo, 1925-2010; Porter, Quincy, 1897-1966; Maturana, Eduardo, 1920-2003; Orrego-Salas, Juan, 1919-; Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980
  - Leedy; Martirano; Penderecki; Reger, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 14)
    Martirano, Salvatore. Mass. Hamburg Radio Choir, Thurn, conductor.
    Leedy, Douglas. Antifonia, no. 2.
    Reger, Max, 1873-1916. Serenades, flute, violin, viola, op. 141a, G major.
    Reger, Max, 1873-1916. Suites, violin, piano, op. 103a, A minor.
    Reger, Max, 1873-1916. Serenades, flute, violin, viola, op. 77a, D major.
    Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933- Fluorescences. Southwest German Radio Orchestra, Rosbaud, conductor.
    Martirano, Salvatore; Norddeutscher Rundfunk. Chor; Thurn, Max (Conductor); Leedy, Douglas; Reger, Max, 1873-1916; Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-; Südwestfunk (Baden-Baden, Germany). Orchester; Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962
  - Berio; Fine; Ibert; Matsushita; Yashiro, circa 1960-1963; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 17)
    Fine, Irving, 1914-1962. Nocturne, harp, string orchestra. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Burgin, conductor. 1962-1963 season.
    Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962. Mouvement Symphonique. Boston Symphony Orchestra, Munch, conductor. First performance. 1963.
    Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003. Serenata.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Canzona da sonare for piano and percussion. Osaka Festival of Contemporary Music. 1960.
    Yashiro, Akio, 1929-1976. Quartet, violins (2), viola, cello. Pro Musica String Quartet of Japan. Osaka Festival of Contemporary Music. 1960.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Stars in Cardea, for flute and piano.
    Fine, Irving, 1914-1962; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Burgin, Richard, 1892-1981; Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962; Munch, Charles, 1891-1968; Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003; Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990; Yashiro, Akio, 1929-1976; Pro Musica String Quartet of Japan
  - Messiaen; Penderecki; Schoeck; Van Anrooy, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 19)
    Schoeck, Othmar, 1886-1957. Elegie.
    Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-. Stanzas.
    Anrooy, Peter van, 1879-1954. Piet Hein.
    Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992. Corps glorieux. Combat de la mort et de la vie.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: CRI, SD 161 (Yehudi Wyner: Concert Duo, Matthew Raimondi and composer).
    Schoeck,, Othmar, 1886-1957; Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-; Anrooy, Peter van, 1879-1954; Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992
  - Andriessen; Flothuis; Hába; Harrison; Henkemans; Holst; Landré; Takemitsu, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 24)
    Andriessen, Hendrik, 1892-1981. Symphonies, no. 2. Utrecht Symphony Orchestra, Hupperts, conductor.
    Landré, Guillaume, 1905-1968. Symphonies, no. 3.
    Hába, Alois, 1893-1973. Nonets, flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, violin, viola, cello, double bass, no. 3, op. 82.
    Henkemans, Hans. Passacaglia and Gigue.
    Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934. Ode to death.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Psalter Sonato.
    Takemitsu, Tōru. Landscape, no. 1
    Andriessen, Hendrik, 1892-1981; Utrechts Stedelijk Orkest; Hupperts, Paul; Landré, Guillaume, 1905-1968; Hába, Alois, 1893-1973; Henkemans, Hans; Flothuis, Marius; Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934; Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003; Takemitsu, Tōru
  - Becerra-Schmidt; Botto; Ginastera; Harris, undated (Box 1, Reel 26)
    Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983. Pampeana, no. 2
    Becerra-Schmidt, Gustavo, 1925-2010. Partitas, no. 2.
    Harris, Roy, 1898-1979. Quintets, piano, violins (2), viola, cello.
    Botto, Carlos, 1923-2004. Capriccios, Op.10.
    Becerra-Schmidt, Gustavo, 1925-2010; Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983; Harris, Roy, 1898-1979; Botto, Carlos, 1923-2004
  - Badings; Erb; Orthel; Stravinsky, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 35)
    Orthel, Léon, 1905-1985. Symphonies, no. 2.
    Erb, Donald, 1927-2008. Sonatas, harpsichord, violins (2), viola, cello.
    Badings, Henk, 1907-1987. Symphonies, no. 8.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Symphonie de Psaumes. Psalm 150 only.
    First movement of a sonata for violin solo (1940). Composer not noted. Juda, violin.
    Orthel, Léon, 1905-1985; Erb, Donald, 1927-2008; Badings, Henk, 1907-1987; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Juda, Jo
  - Flothuis; Morowetz; Novak; Ravel, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 36)
    Novak, Lionel. Sonata No.3 for cello and piano. Novak, piano. Cellist was performer for whom the work was written for.
    Morowetz, Oscar. Symphony No.2. Canadian Broadcasting Symphony Orchestra, Feldbrill, conductor.
    Flothuis, Marius. Symfonische muziek.
    Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Gaspard de la nuit. Ondine. Jablonski, piano.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: CRI, CRI 123 (Shifrin Serenade).
    Novak, Lionel; Morowetz, Oscar; Flothuis, Marius; Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937; Jablonski, Marek; CBC Symphony Orchestra; Feldbrill, Victor
  - Goeb: Symphony No.4. Dallapiccola: Six carmina Alcaei. Górecki: Symphony No.1, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 1, Reel 39)
    Goeb, Roger, 1914-1997. Symphonies, no. 4.
    Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1904-1975. Liriche greche. Carmina Alcaei.
    Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1904-1975. Requiescant.
    Górecki, Henryk Mikołaj, 1933-2010. Symphonies, no. 1, op. 14. Polish Radio Symphony of Katowice, Krenz, conductor.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: CRI, CRI 167 (Druckman, Dark upon the harp).
    Goeb, Roger, 1914-1997; Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1904-1975; Polskie Radio. Wielka Orkiestra Symfoniczna; Krenz, Jan, 1926-
  - Baird; Boulez; Kolb; Milhaud; Stravinsky; Togni, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 41)
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Concertos, viola, orchestra, no. 1, op. 108. De Pasquale, violin; Boston Symphony Orchestra, Leinsdorf, conductor.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Concertino, violins (2), viola, cello. Bass Quartet.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Erotyki.
    Togni, Camillo. Helian di Trakl. Dorow, soprano; BBC Symphony Orchestra, Rosbaud, conductor. ICSM, London. 1962.
    Boulez, Pierre, 1925- Poésie pour pouvoir. Bouquet, speaker; Rosbaud, conductor.
    Boulez, Pierre, 1925- Etudes, tape, no. 1.
    Kolb, Barbara. Rebuttal. Kolb and Kochineas, clarinets.
    Kolb, Barbara. Three songs on poems by Arthur Cloutier. Tregar, baritone; Epstein, piano.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: Donemus, DAVS 6401 (Hans Henkemans Partita, Concertgebouw).
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974.; De Pasquale, Joseph; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Bass Quartet; Togni, Camillo; BBC Symphony Orchestra; Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962; Dorow, Dorothy; Boulez, Pierre, 1925-; Kolb, Barbara; Kochineas, Peter; Tregar, Philip; Epstein, Alvin; Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981; Bouquet, Michel
  - Badings; Matsushita; Prokofiev; Winkler, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 43)
    Badings, Henk, 1907–1987. Symphonic variations. Concertgebouw, Van Beinum, conductor.
    Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Concertos, piano, 1 hand, orchestra, op. 53, B♭ major. Vedernikov, piano; Giusburg, conductor.
    Winkler, Peter, 1943-. Sonata for cello and piano.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Uro for piano, string quartet, and percussion.
    Badings, Henk, 1907-1987; Beinum, Eduard van; Concertgebouworkest; Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953; Winkler, Peter, 1943-; Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990
  - Cilèa: Adriana Lecouvreur, act1 and 2, 1977-09-16; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips; stereo; dolby] (Box 1, Reel 44)
    Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Adriana Lecouvreur. Acts 1 and 2. San Francisco Opera. Live broadcast.
  - Baird: Exorde. Ashley: Fourth of July. Ishii: Sonata for viola and piano, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 45)
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Exorde for speaker, choir and orchestra.
    Ashley, Robert, 1930-2014. 4th of July.
    Ishii, Kan, 1921-2009. Sonata for viola and piano.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981; Ashley, Robert, 1930-2014; Ishii, Kan, 1921-2009
  - Akio; Baird; Freeman; Janáček, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 46)
    Yashiro, Akio, 1929-1976. Symphony.
    Janáček, Leoš, 1854-1928. Mša glagolskaja.
    Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981. Divertimento, flute, oboe, clarinet, bassoon.
    Freedman, Harry, 1922-2005. Wind quintet.
    Yashiro, Akio, 1929-1976; Janáček, Leoš, 1854-1928; Baird, Tadeusz, 1928-1981; Freedman, Harry, 1922-2005
  - Erickson; Hindemith; Miyoshi; Toyama, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 48)
    Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963. Serenaden.
    Erickson. Concerto for orchestra.
    Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013. Concertos, piano, orchestra.
    Toyama. Violin concerto.
    Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963; Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013
  - Irino; Mamiyal; Miyoshi; Moroi; Respighi; Takemitsu, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 50)
    Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980. Double concerto for piano, violin, and orchestra.
    Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013. Three symphonic movements for orchestra.
    Moroi, Makoto, 1930-2013. Schönberg shō [Ode to Schoenberg].
    Takemitsu, Tōru. Ring, for flute, guitar, and lute. Osaka Festival.
    Mamiya, Michio, 1929- Composition for mixed chorus.
    Respighi, Ottorino, 1879-1936. Lauda per la Natività del Signore.
    Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980; Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013; Moroi, Makoto, 1930-2013; Takemitsu, Tōru; Mamiya, Michio, 1929-; Respighi, Ottorino, 1879-1936
  - Japanese music presentation at the University of Washington. Mayuzumi: String quartet, circa 1964; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 51)
    Japanese music program at the University of Washington. Presented by Robert Garfias. KRAB. 1964.
    Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997. String quartet.
    Garfias, Robert; Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997
  - Fukui; Irino; Koyama; Mamiya; Matsushita; Miyoshi; Nakada; Shimizu; Ugazin, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 52)
    Irino, Yoshirō, 1921–1980. Three mixed choruses on folk songs of the Tchuku District.
    Fukui, Fumihiko, 1909-1976. Mogamigawa funauta.
    Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013. Murder case.
    Nakada, Yoshinao, 1923-2000. Composition of the sea.
    Shimizu, Osamu, 1911-1986. Visons.
    Ugazin, Mitsutoshi. Shogoro Odori (folksong of Ibusuki District).
    Koyama, Kiyoshige, 1914-2009. Lion dance of Province of Ichiko.
    Mamiya, Michio, 1929- Taburō (1965). Iwaki, conductor.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Three tempi for eleven instruments.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Torso standing in the twilight.
    Irino, Yoshirō, 1921-1980; Fukui, Fumihiko, 1909-1976; Miyoshi, Akira, 1933-2013; Nakada, Yoshinao, 1923-2000; Shimizu, Osamu, 1911-1986; Ugazin, Mitsutoshi; Koyama, Kiyoshige, 1914-2009; Mamiya, Michio, 1929-; Iwaki, Hiroyuki; Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990
  - Jolivet; Ketting; Matsushita; Radica; Salzedo, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 61)
    Jolivet, André, 1905-1974. Concertos, percussion, orchestra.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Uro.
    Ketting, Otto, 1935-2012. Canzoni, orchestra. Radio Chamber Orchestra, Kroll, conductor.
    Radica, Ruben, 1931- Lyric variations. Op.8. ICSM, London. 1962.
    Salzedo, Carlos, 1885-1961. Poèmes de Stéphane Mallarmé.
    Jolivet, André, 1905-1974; Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990; Ketting, Otto, 1935-2012; Radica, Ruben, 1931-; Salzedo, Carlos, 1885-1961; Radio Kamerorkest (Nederlandse Omroepprogramma Stichting); Kroll, Rudolf
  - Cilenšek; Kochan; Rudziński; Sikorski; Takemitsu, circa 1963-1964; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 62)
    Takemitsu, Tōru. Music of tree.
    Cilenšek, Johann, 1913-1998. Symphonies, no. 4. East Berlin Radio Symphony Orchestra, Kleinert, conductor.
    Sikorski, Tomasz, 1939-1988. Prologi. Warsaw Philharmonic Chorus and Ensemble, Kuklewicz, conductor. Warsaw Festival. 1963 or 1964.
    Rudziński, Zbigniew, 1935- Contra fidem. Silesian Philharmonic, Stryja, conductor. Warsaw Festival. 1964.
    Kochan, Günter. Violin concerto. Gawriloff, violin; Berlin Radio Symphony Orchestra, Konwitschny, conductor.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: RCA Victor, LM 1778 (Dvorak Symphony No. 5: Toscanini: NBC Orchestra).
    Takemitsu, Tōru; Cilenšek, Johann, 1913-1998; Berliner Rundfunk. Sinfonie-Orchester; Kleinert, Rolf; Sikorski, Tomasz, 1939-1988; Rudziński, Zbigniew, 1935-; Filharmonia Narodowa (Warsaw, Poland). Zespół Kameralistów; Kuklewicz, Roman; Filharmonia Narodowa (Warsaw, Poland). Chór; Orkiestra Symfoniczna Filharmonii Śląskiej; Stryja, Karol, 1915-1998; Kochan, Günter; Gawriloff, Saschko; Berliner Rundfunk. Sinfonie-Orchester; Konwitschny, Franz, 1901-1962
  - Krenek: Jonny spielt auf. Kochan: Piano concerto, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips] (Box 1, Reel 70)
    Krenek, Ernst, 1900-1991. Jonny spielt auf.
    Kochan, Günter. Concertos, piano, orchestra, op. 16.
    Krenek, Ernst, 1900-1991; Kochan, Günter
  - Bekku; Matsushita; Moroi; Ogura, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 71)
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990. Life symphony.
    Ogura, Rō, 1916-1990. Sonatina for strings.
    Moroi, Makoto, 1930-2013. Five epigrams.
    Bekku, Sadao, 1922-2012. Sinfonietta, string orchestra.
    Matsushita, Shinʼichi, 1922-1990; Ogura, Rō, 1916-1990; Moroi, Makoto, 1930-2013; Bekku, Sadao, 1922-2012
  - Bach; Couperin; Della Ciaja; Philidori; Purcell; Telemann, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 75)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Geist und Seele wird verwirret. Selections; arranged. [Concertos, harpsichord, oboe, string orchestra, BWV 1059, D minor]. Leonhardt, arranger. Geraint Jones Orchestra. Transcription from BBC broadcast by KPFA. January 10, 1962.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichords (2), string orchestra, BWV 1061, C major; arranged. Leonhardt, arranger. Geraint Jones Orchestra. Transcription from BBC broadcast by KPFA. January 10, 1962.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Concerts royaux. No 4. Rampal, flute; Veyron-Lacroix, harpsichord. Transcription from BBC broadcast by KPFA. January 10, 1962.
    Della Ciaja, Azzolino Bernardino, 1671-1755. Toccata, keyboard instrument. Gerlin, harpsichord.
    Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767. Trio sonata in G minor for recorder, oboe and harpsichord. Jones, harpsichord. CBC.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Mein Herze schwimmt im Blut.
    Philidor, Anne Danican, 1681-1728. Livre de pièces, 1er livre. Sonata, recorder, continuo. Wollitz, recorder; Dessler, cello; White, harpsichord. KPFA live broadcast. November 27, 1962.
    Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695. We sing to Him whose wisdom form'd the ear. Cohen, soprano; Dessler, cello; White, harpsichord. KPFA live broadcast. November 27, 1962.
    Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695. If music be the food of love (1692). Realized by Britten. Cohen, soprano; Dessler, cello; White, harpsichord. KPFA live broadcast. November 27, 1962.
    Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695. Lord, what is man? Cohen, soprano; Dessler, cello; White, harpsichord. KPFA live broadcast. November 27, 1962.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Leonhardt, Gustav, 1928-; Geraint Jones Orchestra; Jones, Geraint, 1917-1998; Couperin, François, 1668-1733; Rampal, Jean-Pierre, 1922-2000; Veyron-Lacroix, Robert; Della Ciaja, Azzolino Bernardino, 1671-1755; Gerlin, Ruggero; Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767; Jones, Kelsey, 1922-2004; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Philidor, Anne Danican, 1681-1728; Dessler, Ellen; Wollitz, Kenneth; White, Angus; Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695; Britten, Benjamin, 1913-1976; Cohen, Eleanor (Singer)
  - Boulez; Henze; Krenek; Lees, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 76)
    Lees, Benjamin, 1924-2010. Concertos, violin, orchestra. Szeryng, violin; Boston Symphony Orchestra, Leinsdorf, conductor.
    Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012. Sonatinas, flute, piano. Polas, flute; Rudolf, piano.
    Boulez, Pierre, 1925- Sonatas, piano, no. 2.
    Krenek, Ernst, 1900-1991. Concertos, cello, orchestra. Second movement only. Hoelscher, cello; Dixon, conductor.
    Lees, Benjamin, 1924-2010; Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012; Szeryng, Henryk; Boston Symphony Orchestra; Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993; Polas, Klaus; Rudolf, Wolfgang; Boulez, Pierre, 1925-; Krenek, Ernst, 1900-1991; Hoelscher, Ludwig; Dixon, Dean, 1915-1976
  - Babbitt; Caltech Glee Club; Milhaud; Stockhausen, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 77)
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007. Momente.
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Cantate de la guerre.
    Babbitt, Milton, 1916-2011. Vision and prayer.
    Caltech Glee Club program.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: CRI, SD 446 (Composition for viola and piano / Milton Babbitt).
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007; Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974; Babbitt, Milton, 1916-2011; Caltech Glee Club
  - Bach: Cantata No.56, circa 1963; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 78)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich will den Kreuzstab gerne tragen. Fischer-Dieskau, baritone; Festival Strings Lucerne. Edinburgh Festival. BBC. Circa 1963.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: Archiv, 13 022 (Bach: Suite G for Lute BWV 995: Walter Gerwig); Columbia, MS 6608 (Bach: Suite E: John Williams).
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-2012; Festival Strings Lucerne
  - Berger; Boulez; Hindemith; Maderna; Nono, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 80)
    Berger, Arthur, 1912-2003. Pieces, pianos (2).
    Composer
    Boulez, Pierre, 1925- Structures, pianos (2), 2e livre.
    Maderna, Bruno. Music for orchestra, No.2.
    Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963. Chansons, mixed voices. Berkeley Chamber Singers, Erb, conductor.
    Nono, Luigi. Sarà dolce tacere.
    Berger, Arthur, 1912-2003; Boulez, Pierre, 1925-; Maderna, Bruno; Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963; Berkeley Chamber Singers; Erb, Donald, 1927-2008; Nono, Luigi
  - Berio; Furtner; Harris; Imbrie; Nilsson; Schuller, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 81)
    Harris, Roy, 1898-1979. Sonatas, piano.
    Imbrie, Andrew, 1921-2007. Sonatas, piano.
    Fortner, Wolfgang, 1907-1987. Bagatelles, flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon.
    Nilsson, Bo. Zwanzig Gruppen.
    Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003. Sequenza, no. 1.
    Schuller, Gunther. Quintets, flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon
    Harris, Roy, 1898-1979; Imbrie, Andrew, 1921-2007; Fortner, Wolfgang, 1907-1987; Nilsson, Bo; Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003; Schuller, Gunther
  - Eisler: Chamber Symphony, Quintet, Nonet No.2, Septet No.2, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 83)
    Eisler, Hanns, 1898-1962. Kammersinfonie. German Radio Symphony Orchestra.
    Eisler, Hanns, 1898-1962. Arten den Regen zu beschreiben. German Radio Symphony Orchestra.
    Eisler, Hanns, 1898-1962. Nonet No.2. German Radio Symphony Orchestra.
    Eisler, Hanns, 1898-1962. Septets, flute, clarinet, bassoon, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 2. German Radio Symphony Orchestra.
    Eisler, Hanns
  - Bridge: Trio. Bush: Dorian passacaglia and fugue. Rodney Bennett: Journal for orchestra, circa 1966; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 89)
    Bridge, Frank, 1879-1941. Trios, piano, violin, cello, no. 2. Menuhin, violin; Gendron, cello; Britten, piano.
    Bush, Alan, 1900-1995. Dorian passacaglia and fugue. BBC Symphony Orchestra; Del Mar or Schwarz, conductor.
    Bennett, Richard Rodney. Journal for orchestra. BBC Symphony Orchestra, Del Mar, conductor. Seventeeth Cheltenham Festival.
    Bridge, Frank, 1879-1941; Menuhin, Yehudi, 1916-1999; Gendron, Maurice; Britten, Benjamin, 1913-1976; Bush, Alan, 1900-1995; BBC Symphony Orchestra; Del Mar, Norman, 1919-1994; Schwarz, Rudolf, 1905-1994; Bennett, Richard Rodney
  - Boulez; Nono; Schuller; Smith, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 99)
    Schuller, Gunther. Quartets, double basses (4).
    Smith, Leland, 1925-2013. Trios, violin, viola, cello. Rubin, violin; James, viola; Hampton, cello.
    Boulez, Pierre, 1925- Sonatina, flute, piano.
    Nono, Luigi. Epitaffio per Federico García Lorca, no. 3.
    Schuller, Gunther; Nono, Luigi; Smith, Leland, 1925-; Boulez, Pierre, 1925-; Rubin, Nathan, 1929-; James, Mary; Hampton, Bonnie
  - Berio; Erickson; Fukushima; Mayuzumi, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 101)
    Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997. Microcosmos, for seven players.
    Fukushima, Kazuo, 1930- Kadha karuna. Takahishi, flute; Koedi, flute; Kanzei, tsuzumi; Hansho, piano.
    Fukushima, Kazuo, 1930- Three pieces for flute and piano. Hayashi, Hiriki, flute; Hayashi, Ikaro, piano.
    Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003. Allelujah, no. 2. Rome Symphony Orchestra, Maderna, conductor.
    Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997. Fantasy, cello, orchestra. Hamburg Orchestra, Krenek, conductor.
    Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997; Fukushima, Kazuo, 1930-; Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003; Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997; Takahishi, Yasuhari; Koedi, Shinya; Kanzei, Isaro; Hansho, Rieko; Hayashi, Hiriki; Hayashi, Ikaro; Maderna, Bruno; Rome Symphony Orchestra; Krenek, Ernst, 1900-1991
  - Friedman; Milhaud; Saeverud; Schat; Svendsen, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 107)
    Svendsen, Johan S. (Johan Severin), 1840-1911. Symphonies, no. 1, op. 4, D major.
    Saeverud, Harald. Sinfonia dolorosa, Op.19.
    Schat, Peter, 1935-2003. Dansen uit het Labyrint.
    Friedman, Harry. Five pieces for string quartet. Vancouver String Quartet.
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 4, op. 46. Vancouver String Quartet.
    This tape also contains dubbed copies of the following commercial releases: Melodram, MEL 204 (Beethoven Sonata No. 10 Szigeti and Schnabel).
    Svendsen, Johan S. (Johan Severin), 1840-1911; Saeverud, Harald; Schat, Peter, 1935-2003; Friedman, Harry; Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974; Vancouver String Quartet
  - Martinů: Sonata for two violins; Sonatina for two violins, 1951; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 1, Reel 111)
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959. Sonatas, piano, violins (2). Schweyde, Willy and Margaret, violins; Behr, piano.
    Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959. Sonatinas, piano, violins (2). Schweyde, Willy and Margaret, violins; Behr, piano.
    This is a dub of a rare LP - Urania Records, URLP 5004.